agilitycms.com 2019-05-13

# Agility CMS | Privacy Policy

Your privacy is critically important to us.  At Agility Inc. (“ **Agility** ”) we have a few fundamental principles:

  * We don’t ask you for personal information unless we truly need it. (We can’t stand services that ask you for things like your gender or income level for no apparent reason.)
  * We don’t share your personal information with anyone except to comply with the law, provide you with our products and services, or protect our rights or the rights of other people.
  * We don’t store personal information on our servers unless required for the on-going operation of one of our services.

Below is our privacy policy which incorporates these principles:[](http://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-sa/2.5/) [](http://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-sa/2.5/)(Note, we’ve decided to make this privacy policy available under a **Creative Commons Sharealike** license, which means you’re more than welcome to steal it and repurpose it for your own use, just make sure to replace references to us with ones to you.)

If you have questions about accessing or correcting your personal data please contact our support team.

Agility operates several websites including agilitycms.com, and contentmanager.agilitycms.com. It is Agility’s policy to respect your privacy regarding any information we may collect while operating our websites.

**What Information Do We Collect?**

Like most website operators, Agility collects non-personal information of the sort that web browsers and servers typically make available, such as the browser type, language preference, referring site, and the date and time of each visitor request. Agility’s purpose in collecting non-personally identifying information is to better understand how Agility’s visitors use its website. From time to time, Agility may release non-personal information in the aggregate, e.g., by publishing a report on trends in the usage of its website.

Agility also collects potentially personal information like Internet Protocol (IP) addresses for logged in users and for users leaving comments on solutions built on contentmanager.agilitycms.com. Agility only discloses logged in user and commenter IP addresses under the same circumstances that it uses and discloses personal information as described below, except that user generated content (“UGC”) IP addresses are visible and disclosed to the administrators of the UGC where the comment was left.

Agility may collect statistics about the behaviour of visitors to its websites. For instance, Agility may monitor the most popular solutions built on Agility. Agility may display this information publicly or provide it to others. However, Agility does not disclose personal information other than as described below.

A cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a visitor’s computer, and that the visitor’s browser provides to the website each time the visitor returns. Agility uses cookies to help Agility identify and track visitors, their usage of Agility website, and their website access preferences. Agility visitors who do not wish to have cookies placed on their computers should set their browsers to refuse cookies before using

Agility’s websites, with the drawback that certain features of Agility’s websites may not function properly without the aid of cookies.

Certain visitors to Agility’s websites choose to interact with Agility in ways that require Agility to gather personal information. The amount and type of information that Agility gathers depends on the nature of the interaction. For example, we ask visitors who sign up for an account at agilitycms.com or contentmanager.agilitycms.com to provide an email address and as well are asked to provide additional information, including as necessary the personal and financial information required to process licensing transactions. In each case, Agility collects such information only insofar as is necessary or appropriate to fulfill the purpose of the visitor’s interaction with Agility. And visitors can always refuse to supply personal information, with the caveat that it may prevent them from engaging in certain website-related activities.

**How Do We Use the Personal Information We Collect?**  

We use personal information in the file we maintain about you, and other information we obtain from your current and past activities on the Site, to provide to you the services offered by the Site; resolve service disputes; troubleshoot problems; measure consumer interest in our products and services, inform you about online and offline offers, products, services, events and updates; deliver information to you that, in some cases, is relevant to your interests, such as product news; customize your experience; detect and protect us against error, fraud and other criminal activity; enforce our Terms of Use; provide you with system or administrative messages, and as otherwise described to you at the time of collection.

We may also use personal information about you to improve our marketing and promotional efforts, to analyze Site usage, to improve our content and product offerings, and to customize the Site's content, layout, and services. These uses improve the Site and better tailor it to meet your needs, so as to provide you with a smooth, efficient, safe and customized experience while using the Site.

If you are a registered user of an Agility website and have supplied your email address, Agility may occasionally send you an email to tell you about new features, solicit your feedback, or just keep you up to date with what’s going on with Agility and our products. We primarily use our various product blogs to communicate this type of information, so we expect to keep this type of email to a minimum. If you send us a request (for example via a support email or via one of our feedback mechanisms), we reserve the right to publish it in order to help us clarify or respond to your request or to help us support other users. Agility takes all measures reasonably necessary to protect against the unauthorized access, use, alteration or destruction of potentially personal and personal information.

**How Do We Disclose Your Personal Information?**

Agility discloses potentially personal and personal information only to those of its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations that (i) need to know that information in order to process it on Agility’s behalf or to provide services available at Agility’s websites, and (ii) that have agreed not to disclose it to others. Some of those employees, contractors and affiliated organizations may be located outside of your home country; by using Agility’s websites, you consent to the transfer of such information to them. Agility will not rent or sell potentially personal and personal information to anyone. Other than to its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations, as described above, Agility discloses potentially personal and personal information only in response to a subpoena, court order or other governmental request, or when Agility believes in good faith that disclosure is reasonably necessary to protect the property or rights of Agility, third parties or the public at large.

**Also,** if Agility, or substantially all of its assets were acquired, or in the unlikely event that Agility goes out of business or enters bankruptcy, user information would be one of the assets that is transferred or acquired by a third party. You acknowledge that such transfers may occur, and that any acquiror of Agility may continue to use your personal information as set forth in this policy.

**GDPR**

Information on our approach to the General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR) can be found here.

**Privacy Policy Changes**

Agility may change its Privacy Policy from time to time, and in Agility’s sole discretion.  If we do, and you are a registered user of our websites. If you have an agilitycms.com pr contentmanager.agilitycms.com account, we will email you at the email address you have registered with us. Agility encourages other visitors to frequently check this page for any changes to its Privacy Policy
